{
  "type": "matching",
  "title": "Matching (1 point each, 15 total)",
  "instructions": "Select the correct response from the dropdown (be sure to scroll all the way down and read CAREFULLY).",
  "points_per_question": 1,
  "prompts": [
    {
      "question": "In the 90s (5th Gen), what was a non-shooter killer app on the PC?",
      "answer": "Myst"
    },
    {
      "question": "What game first popularized the first person shooter genre?",
      "answer": "Doom"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who invented the predecessor to Monopoly in 1903, The Landlord's Game?",
      "answer": "Elizabeth Magie"
    },
    {
      "question": "What happened in the late 70s and early 80s for electronic gaming?",
      "answer": "The Rise of Arcades"
    },
    {
      "question": "What action-adventure survival did very poorly on initial release but slowly built up a base?",
      "answer": "No Man's Sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "Games prior to the 19th century were primarily ________ games",
      "answer": "Multi-Player"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who pioneered the ability to play multiple games on a single console?",
      "answer": "Jerry Lawson"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ is an interactive proof of concept that includes as many game mechanics (usually not feature complete) as possible to let players understand what the final game will be like.",
      "answer": "Vertical Slice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was created in response to violence and graphic imagery in video games?",
      "answer": "ESRB"
    },
    {
      "question": "Independent companies that create games but do not publish them are called.",
      "answer": "Third-Party Developers"
    },
    {
      "question": "The number of copies a product actually sold.",
      "answer": "Sell-through"
    },
    {
      "question": "A way to market your game using real world clues and mystery to promote it.",
      "answer": "Alternate Reality Game"
    },
    {
      "question": "What historical industry event partially inspired the Mario & Sonic at the Olympic Games series?",
      "answer": "The Console Wars"
    },
    {
      "question": "First successful game company founded in 1860 that also invented the Microvision handheld console?",
      "answer": "Milton Bradley"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company did Nolan Bushnell and Ted Dabney found?",
      "answer": "Atari"
    }
    
  ],
  "word_bank": [
    { "text": "Elizabeth Magie" },
    { "text": "Charles Darrow" },
    { "text": "Ralph Baer"},
    { "text": "Jerry Lawson"},
    { "text": "The Rise of Arcades" },
    { "text": "The Crash and Recovery of the Game Industry" },
    { "text": "The Console Wars"},
    { "text": "Quake" },
    { "text": "Myst" },
    { "text": "Doom" },
    { "text": "No Man's Sky"},
    { "text": "The Outer Worlds"},
    { "text": "Multi-Player"},
    { "text": "Single-Player"},
    { "text": "Prototypes"},
    { "text": "Vertical Slice"},
    { "text": "GDD"},
    { "text": "Project Plan"},
    { "text": "ESRB" },
    { "text": "IGDA" },
    { "text": "First-Party Developers"},
    { "text": "Third-Party Developers"},
    { "text": "Publishers" },
    { "text": "Sell-in" },
    { "text": "Sell-through" },
    { "text": "Alternate Reality Game" },
    { "text": "Viral Marketing" },
    { "text": "Milton Bradley" },
    { "text": "Parker Brothers"},
    { "text": "Atari" },
    { "text": "Nintendo" }
    

    
  ]
}
